RG 041:002, Public Utilities Commission
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Miscellaneous Records, 1911-1924; .5 cubic feet; 1932-075 except where noted
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Stenographer's Minutes, 2014-021; .5 cubic feet (3 volumes)
    - Investigation of the collision between first and second sections of train no. 53 on the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, near Stamford, Connecticut, June 12th, 1913. At Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1913 June 18; 1 volume (Volume Item 2)
    - In the matter of the investigation of the accident on the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, near Wallingford, Connecticut, on September 2, 1913. At New Haven, Connecticut, 1913 September 5-6; 1 volume (Volume Item 3)